myopenrouter.com 2017-06-03

# Privacy Policy | MyOpenRouter

At [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/),, we know that your privacy is important to you and we take it very seriously. We are also motivated to provide the best experience for you and this is often achieved by learning more about you and from tracking the collective activity or our membership. This statement describes the ways in which we collect and use information about you at our website, techlore.com ("site").

**Tracking Member Activity**

We do not collect any personal information about our users other than when you explicitly provide it to us or when it is reasonably needed in the operation of our site and/or our business. We track your activity on the site as you discover and consume the content in order to help customize your experience. Each time you log into the site, your profile is updated to reflect your actions in that session. Through the use of cookies (a small piece of data stored on your computer by your Internet browser) and other techniques, we can further improve your experience by automating the login process. It is not necessary for you to have cookies enabled in order to explore our site; however, you must have registered and logged in to access many of the site's advanced features. The information in the browser cookie does not present any additional privacy concern outside of facilitating automatic login to our site and setting of user preferences. It is highly recommended to enable cookies to improve your overall experience. We may also collect, analyze and store general statistical information of your usage of the site (such as your IP address, browser type, originating domain names, access times and referring website addresses).

Through our site, you may publish, rate or discuss content such as an article, quick tip, or a forum topic. In most cases your content and information will be made publicly available to the website community unless specified differently in your user configuration. By contributing to the community in this way, you are giving [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), permission to republish and use this information as per the [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/),' User Agreement

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this site, other web sites and other forms of media in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here **.**

****Member Data****

The primary goal of collecting information about our users is to help us provide a more targeted and useful experience for all users of the site, so we encourage users to provide us with personal information in order to help build the community and demographic aspects of the site. [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), only collects personal information with the user's explicit permission. BY PROVIDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US YOU ARE EXPRESSLY CONSENTING TO OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR ALL OF THE PURPOSES SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND FOR ANY OTHER ADDITIONAL PURPOSES THAT MAY BE SET FORTH ON THE SITE. Most of this information is collected during the registration process and when you provide it to us by updating your profile. We may also receive certain information about you from third parties that we may add to your profile. Individual information that can be tied back to a specific user will never be sold, leased, or rented to a third party except when we receive explicit permission from the user to do so.

****Emails****

[Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), uses member data and information collected during the registration process for many purposes including targeted advertising and email newsletters. You can configure your account to turn advertising emails on and off; however, administrative emails, such as those that communicate updates to our policies and agreements, are not optional while you have an active account.

In certain places of our site, you are given the ability to send emails to other users. You supply the email address of the receiver and an optional personal note. These emails and related information are not retained nor used in any way other than to send the email as requested. We will not solicit the recipients of these email messages.

****IP Information****

When visiting our website, we reserve the right to store and use your IP address.

****Polls and Surveys****

Periodically, [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), conducts user surveys and polls and performs other related campaigns on our website. We reserve the right to sell the aggregate information obtained from these surveys to our sponsors or other interested third parties or use the data in the promotion, marketing and/or customization of our site. No personally identifiable information that may be tracked back to an individual is sold to any third parties. If you prefer that your information not be used in this aggregate way, then it is recommended that you do not participate in these activities.

****Privacy Policies Of Third Party Websites****

The site may contain hyperlinks to third party websites, and while [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), makes all reasonable efforts to hyperlink to websites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of third party websites. As such, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the site so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.

****Children****

Our website is not intended or directed at any children who are twelve years of age and under. We operate in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act as posted during the registration process. We do not permit registration nor knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone 12 years of age or under. If you are 12 years of age or under, please do not use our site.

****Disclosure****

We reserve the right to disclose any personal information about you or your use of the site, including its contents, without your prior permission if we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of [Magenium Solutions](http://magenium.com/), or its affiliated companies; (3) enforce the site terms or use or any other agreement between you and us; or (4) act to protect the interests of its users and customers. Our performance of this policy is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this policy is in derogation of our right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the site or information provided to or gathered by us with respect to such use. Further, we may sell your personal information in a sale of all or substantially all of our assets or in the event of a change in control.

****Security Of Personal Information****

All Personal Information is protected by current security technology in an effort to safeguard your Personal Information. ? Nonetheless, we are not responsible for any breach of its security or for the actions of any third parties that may obtain any Personal Information. See our Terms of Use and Notices also at  

**Removal, Review And Correction**

Site users may remove their Personal Information from our distribution lists by contacting our Customer Service department.

**Please click here to submit our online form**

****Changes****

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying site users of the existence of a new Privacy Policy or any updates by posting a notice at this location or by e-mail or by any other reasonable means.

****Contact Information****

We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy.

**Please click here to submit our online form**
